"lang"
{
"Language"	"korean"
"Tokens"
{
"ball_mod_ai.bed_intro_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>애퍼처 과학 강화 센터 자동 실험 감금 계획의 999번째 세션에 오신 것을 환영합니다. 강제 동면기를 거친 당신은 좋은 휴식의 결과로 상쾌한 기분을 느낄 것입니다."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.bed_intro_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Good morning and welcome to session 999 of your Aperture Science Enrichment Center automated testing confinement.  You should be feeling rested and refreshed after your forced hibernation period."
"ball_mod_ai.bed_intro_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>귀하의 휴식 중 자사의 특허받은 기억 상실증 독정물질이 뇌 속의 최근에 연결된 뉴런들에 영향을 끼쳐 과거의 경험에서 비롯된 공포와 분노가 조성한 공포증이나 불안감은 현재 액체 상태로 귀하의 척추 상부의-"
"[english]ball_mod_ai.bed_intro_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>As you rested, our patented amnesia inducing toxins have slowly worn away at your brain's recently connected neurons, making any fears or anxieties you might have from the horror and or agony of what you have previously experienced, melt away into a viscous fluid which now resides in your upper spinal-"
"ball_mod_ai.bed_intro_03"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>방해해서 미안해. 독성물질 때문에 기억을 못하겠지만 어떤 피실험자가 자폭 장치를 가동시켜서 시설을 많이 파괴했거든. 걱정 마. 실험은 계속할 테니까. 어서 끈질기고 지루한 정보나 들으러 가자."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.bed_intro_03"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>Pardon the interruption.  You probably don't remember much due to the brain chemicals, but a certain test subject managed to trigger a self-destruct sequence and destroy a large section of the facility.  There's no need to worry.  Testing will resume.  Let's get back to the tedious informational nonsense."
"ball_mod_ai.bed_intro_04"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>-그리고 남은 분비물들은 바로 채집하여 분석하도록 해 주십시오. 이제 휴대용 포털 장치를 가지고 진행하세요."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.bed_intro_04"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>-and any remaining bodily fluids should be captured and immediately sent for analysis.  Please pick up the handheld portal device to proceed."
"ball_mod_ai.intro_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>좋습니다. 포털이 귀하를 어떻게 이동시키는 지에 대한 기본적인 지식을 갖추셨습니다. 다음 구역으로 진행하세요."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.intro_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Good.  You appear to have a basic understanding of how portals can move you through space.  Please continue to the next area."
"ball_mod_ai.pellet_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>좌측을 보시면 비임계질량 에너지 펠릿이 있습니다. 귀하의 휴대용 포털 장치를 이용해 에너지 펠릿을 고밀도 전자 분해기로 전송시켜 주십시오."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.pellet_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>To your left you will see a sub-critical mass energy pellet.  Please use your handheld portal device to direct the energy pellet into the high concentration electron dispersal unit."
"ball_mod_ai.intro_end_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>훌륭합니다. 이 펠릿 추출기에서 얻은 에너지는 예를 들어 다음 실험실로 가는 엘리베이터의 전력원처럼 좋은 곳에 사용될 것입니다. 그리고 탈수로 인한 증상이 발생하기 전까지 모든 실험을 완료하려면 43시간이 남았음을 기억해 주십시오. 행운을 빕니다."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.intro_end_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Excellent.  The energy produced by this pellet extractor will be sent to a worthy cause, namely the elevator to the next chamber.  Remember, you have approximately 43 hours to complete these tests before the symptoms of dehydration start to kick in.  Good luck."
"ball_mod_ai.holder_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>중량 큐브를 1500메가와트 자기유체역학적 큐브 안정성 장치 위에 놓아 주십시오. 이것으로 에너지 펠릿의 진행방향을 바꿀 수 있습니다."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.holder_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Please place the weighted storage cube into the 1500 megawatt hydromagnetic cube stability unit.  This will allow you to change the path of the energy pellet."
"ball_mod_ai.holder_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>에너지 펠릿이 자기유체역학적 큐브 안정성 장치의 잘못된 면과 접촉할 경우 에너지 펠릿이 파괴된다는 것을 참고해 주십시오."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.holder_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Note that any energy pellet will be destroyed if it comes in contact with the wrong side of a hydromagnetic cube stability unit."
"ball_mod_ai.holder_03"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>좋습니다. 귀하는 중량 큐브의 특성과 큐브가 에너지 펠릿의 진행 방향에 어떤 영향을 주는지 이해하는 데 성공했습니다. 이러한 실험들에서 중량 큐브의 파괴는 자주 발생하며 몇백만 달러어치의 중량 큐브를 파괴하는 것이 귀하의 점수에 영향을 주지는 않습니다."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.holder_03"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Good.  You appear to understand the nature of the weighted storage cubes and how they can deflect the energy pellets.  Destroying the weighted storage cubes is often required for these tests, and you will not lose points based on how many millions of dollars worth of weighted storage cube technology you destroy."
"ball_mod_ai.destroyer_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>1600메가와트 양전자 에너지 구체에 접근하지 말아 주십시오. 양전자 방사능은 뇌출혈, 망막 발열, 극초단파 내상 증후군, 폐의 폭발 그리고 죽음을 초래할 수 있습니다."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.destroyer_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Please do not approach the 1600 megawatt positron energy orb.  The positron radiation can cause brain hemorrhages, retinal boiling, internal microwave syndrome, minor lung explosions, and eventually death."
"ball_mod_ai.destroyer_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>아까 말한 증상들 중 하나를 겪고 계시다면 좋은 소식으로는 탈수를 걱정하지 않으셔도 된다는 것입니다."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.destroyer_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>If you experience any of the symptoms mentioned previously, then good news, you probably won't need to worry about dehydration."
"ball_mod_ai.temporary_01"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>이거 기억나? 우리가 너의... 음... 뇌에 아주 많이 넣은 뇌신경독 때문에 초록색 에너지 펠릿이 왜 특별한 지 기억해내기 힘들 거야."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.temporary_01"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>Do you remember these?  Due to all those brain chemicals we pumped into your... um... brain... you will probably have a difficult time recollecting what makes the green energy pellets special."
"ball_mod_ai.temporary_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>초록색 에너지 펠릿의 차이점은 반감기가 325만 4800년인 것입니다. 즉 생존 시간으로 비교하여 귀하보다 325만 4700년 더 살 수 있다는 뜻이거나... 단추에서 압력을 제거하면 사라지게 된다는 뜻입니다."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.temporary_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>The green energy pellets are different in that they have a half-life of 3.25428 million years.  In other words, their lifetime is longer than yours by 3.25427 million years... or until you remove pressure from the button."
"ball_mod_ai.temporary_03"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>매우 지혜로운 사실을 알려줘서 고마워, 위키피디아. 그녀가 직접 알아챌 때까지 기다리고 있었거든."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.temporary_03"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>Thanks for the insightful facts, Wikipedia.  I was going to let her figure it out on her own."
"ball_mod_ai.temporary_04"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>환상적이군요. 실험실 출구로 진행해 주십시오."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.temporary_04"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Fantastic.  Please continue to the chamber exit."
"ball_mod_ai.incidence_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>이 실험실은 현재 귀하가 배운 모든 것을 시험할 것입니다. 초록색 에너지 펠릿이 외부의 영향 없이는 지속적으로 존재한다는 것을 잊지 마십시오."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.incidence_01"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>This chamber will test what you have learned so far.  Remember:  green energy pellets will last indefinitely without outside intervention."
"ball_mod_ai.incidence_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>축하드립니다. 귀하가 3학년 수준의 문제를 해결할 수 있다는 것을 증명하셨습니다. 출구로 이동해 주십시오."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.incidence_02"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Congratulations.  You have proven that you can solve puzzles at a third grade level.  Please proceed to the exit."
"ball_mod_ai.incidence_03"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>방금 그건 거짓말이 아냐. 이 실험은 아이들을 위해 설계됐거든. 대부분의 피실험자들은 14세가 적령기지만, 너는 수 년간의 뇌와 관절의 퇴화를 겪고도 성공했어."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.incidence_03"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>He's telling the truth you know.  This test was designed for children.  Most test subjects peak at around 14 years of age, but you were still able to do it after several more years of brain deterioration and joint decay."
"ball_mod_ai.moat_01"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>이건 평범한 실험이 아냐. 이 실험의 목적은 이 시설에 전력이 나간 부분에 전력을 보충하는 게 목적이지. 하지만 내가 너의 매우 큰 실수를 만회하도록 돕는 것뿐이라는 걸 잊지는 마."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.moat_01"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>This isn't a completely normal test run.  The point of these tests is to restore power to the powerless sections of the facility.  You should keep in mind however that you are simply helping me undo your massive failure."
"ball_mod_ai.moat_02"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>이 실험을 완료하면 애퍼처 사이언스 소아부에 전력을 공급해 줄 수 있어. 거기 있는 불쌍한 아이들은... 뭐, 지금은 어른이 됐겠지만, (그리고... 아마도 벌써 죽었을지도 모르지만) 아직도 자동화 풍진 예방 접종을 기다리고 있지."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.moat_02"	"<clr:219,112,147><I>This test chamber, if completed, will restore power to the Aperture Science pediatric wing.  Those poor children, well... probably adults by now, (and... probably not still alive) are patiently awaiting their automated Rubella inoculations."
"ball_mod_ai.moat_03"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>실험을 완료한 것을 축하드립니다. 이 에너지 펠릿은 애퍼처 사이언스 소아부에 5일간 전력을 공급할 것입니다. 그곳의 아픈 아이들이 말을 할 수 있었으면 귀하에게 감사를 표했을 것입니다."
"[english]ball_mod_ai.moat_03"	"<clr:205,129,40><I>Congratulations on completing this test.  This single energy pellet will power the Aperture Science pediatric wing for 5 days.  The sick children would thank you if they could speak."
}
}
